DAN MORRISS

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- **L** +44 7919 288949
- danielmorrissl@gmail.com
- Wiltshire, UK
- www.danmorriss.co.uk

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Junior Software Developer with a Diploma in Full Stack Software Development from the Code Institute. Proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript & Python. I have 15 years experience using technology in the Music Industry. I am a valuable teamplayer with strong communication skills and effective problem solving abilities. I am eager to gain entry into an exciting development team where I can grow and contribute.

EDUCATION

Code Institute

March 2023 - 2024

Full Stack Software Development Diploma

University of West London

Sept 2018 - 2019

Licentiate (Level 6 Degree) in Music Tuition

WORK EXPERIENCE

Director & Music Tutor

Morriss Music Ltd. March 2019 - Present

- Built a website & blog for selling sheet music & courses that grew my credibility.
- Architected smooth booking & invoicing systems, allowing students to manage lessons & payments easily.
- Created an online ukulele course with interactive practice capabilities allowing my student base to grow.

Electric Guitar Tutor & Studio Manager

Cheam School / October 2019 - April 2022

- Arranged and recorded live performances resulting in music scholarships for students.
- Mentored school pop and jazz bands for performances and tours.
- Wrote individual learning paths for students to achieve high exam grades resulting in extra UCAS points.

Session Musician

September 2016 - March 2019

- Demonstrated strong problem-solving skills in highpressure live situations.
- Worked in multiple recording studios utilising digital & outboard recording equipment under strict deadlines.
- Effectively collaborated with numerous musicians live on stage, radio and television.

SKILLS

- → HTML
- → CSS
- → JavaScript
- → Python
- → PostgreSQL
- → React
- → Django
- → Django Rest Framework
- → Bootstrap
- → Git

COURSES

JS30

Wes Boz JavaScript (30 Hours)

Concering Responsive Layouts

Kevin Powell CSS (30 Hours)

Complete React Developer

Redux, Hooks, GraphQL, Stripe, Firebase (42 hours)

PORTFOLIO

Highlights

Social media app built using React & Django REST Framework

Niall's Barber Shop

Booking system for a local barbershop built with Django & PostgreSQL

Retro Mashup Mayhem

Hackathon project: Retro JavaScript platform game built with Kaboom.js